backgroundlabs.com 2019-05-30

# Privacy Policy - Background Labs

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Backgroundlabs.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users. This privacy policy applies to the website and and services offered by Backgroundlabs.com

Information We Collect

**User-Provided Information** : You provide us information about yourself, such as your name, e-mail address. If you correspond with us by email, e process personal information collected for the purposes of dealing with your inquiries and requests.

**Information Collected through cookies** : We use cookies to identify your browser, the type of computer and technical information about user’s means of connection to our website.

**Log File Information** : Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page.

We process personal information collected for the purposes of dealing with your inquiries and optimization.

**Third Party Analytics Services** : We use Google Analytics and you can see how Google uses data when you use our Service and how you may opt out: www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/. For further information about how Google Analytics uses cookies and IP address data, see http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html.

We may collect **non-personal identification information** about users whenever they interact with our Website. The non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about user’s means of connection to our Website, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider’s utilized and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form. This helps us to optimize user’s experience on our website.

Web browser cookies

Our website use cookies to enhance user experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. The user may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the website may not function properly.

We use cookies to order our templates by hits and maintain the most popular list. We limit the number of hits per 24 hours with sessions IDs.

Our website uses cookies/advertising IDs for the purpose of advertising. This enables us to show our advertisements to visitors who are interested in our products on partner websites, apps, and emails.

Re-targeting technologies use your cookies or advertising IDs and display advertisements based on your past browsing behavior.
